Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Archie!
Hands up who wants to know
what happened to me arm.
Okay, okay! Put 'em down.
Just bloody showing off!
No, I left it up in Turkey
back in '15.
I was running
back to the dug-out
with Percy Sullivan on me back
when a shell popped
right next to us.
I lost my arm at the elbow,
Percy lost his head
at the neck.
Pretty soon, you boys
will be sailing into war.
And in that place,
there is no king,
no country,
and there's no fucking honor.
There is only you.
And your mates.
Now, you have
four hours
to get back to camp.
And if a single one of you
is even one minute late,
you will do it again and again
until you get it right!
Now, fall out
and get running.
What the hell are you
simple pricks waiting for?
Pick up ya feet and run,
you bastards! Run!
Come on! Run!
Get up, mate!
Get up!
Come on!
-Come on!
-Come on, boys!
Come on!
Come on. Get up there! Get up!
Come on, lads!
Move, you bastards! Come on!
Come on!
Mate, give us a hand.
Fucking prick!
Come on, boys! Let's go!
-Come on! Move it!
-Come on, move it!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Help!
Here. Here.
You're all right,
you're all right.
Just breathe. Sit up.
-You all right?
-Oi!
Youse two get the fuck up
and get moving!
We're coming!
Well, fucking double-time it,
darkie!
Right, listen.
I'm gonna hump
your pack for you, all right?
Okay. Here we go.
I need you to stand up,
I need you to run.
You all right?
Thanks. I'm Will.
Leo. Move.
Come on, fuck youse!
Keep running!
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one!
Righto, you two.
Head to the mess tent,
get some oranges into you.
Take a load off.
The rest of you...
back on your feet.
You still got work to do.
How is it them two
get out of it, eh?
Stand to attention!
Do you think anyone here
gives a monkey's ass crack
what you think,
shit for brains?
That soldier...
He helped his mate, didn't he?
On the battlefield,
all you've got are your mates.
Now, he knows that.
So why don't you?
Move! Now!
Move! Move, you bastards!
Move!
Down, up. Down, up,
down, up, down, up, down...
Up... All in time!
Down, up, down.
On guard, thrust!
Lads, here we have
our spike trap.
Here is our tripwire.
Here we go.
Today's lesson is explosives.
I have a bag full of them
right here.
When I pull this cord,
you will see an explosion.
Fire in the hole!
Ready!
Aim!
Fire! Reload!
Hey, Bennet!
You ever killed anyone?
Killed a goanna once.
Does that count?
You scared?
No.
Yeah.
It's all right to be afraid.
Fear can keep you alive.
Or it can get you killed.
It's up to you
to know the difference.
Pull the bag up, you coconut!
Here we go.
I wanna go down.
Archie, come on.
This is deep water now.
And there's very
old things out here.
Very old and very dangerous.
You don't dive
till you're ready.
Put your hand up
if you've ever snuck up
behind a man in the dark
and killed him
with a six-inch blade.
Put your hand down,
Dupinski, you bloody idiot!
Thompson, get over here.
Stand there. Facing away.
Okay.
So, I approach thusly,
I pull my knife,
I grab numbnuts here like this.
And I stab the bastard
right... here.
Through the side of the throat
near the Adam's apple.
Severs the carotid.
Kills him instantly.
Now, you sorry buggers
have a crack, eh?
I said silently!
You bloody idiots!
Run it again!
Come on, mate.
Don't be shy.
Kelly, what the bloody hell
are you doin'?
Sorry, Sarge. Arm slipped.
Sorry, Sarge. Boot slipped.
Get the dopey lad!
Kick me in the balls, will you?
Hey! You drop that weapon
right now, soldier!
-Get him!
-Go on! Get him!
What the fuck? Where'd he go?
Can't find him, Sarge!
You locate that man
on the double,
or you're
in some deep shit, son.
Here, darkie, darkie, darkie...
Here, darkie, darkie, darkie.
Maybe a croc took him
or something?
Permission to visit
the medical tent, Sarge?
Ooh!
Hey, can I visit
the medical tent too, Sarge?
Nah...
Don't move your head,
Private.
It's Leo.
If I don't move my head,
then I can't look at you.
You don't need to look at me,
Private.
You need to keep still.
What do they call you
back at home?
They call me Lieutenant Connell.
Now, please don't move.
Her name's Hazel.
Hazel?
-That's a beautiful name.
-M'lady.
Almost as beautiful as you are.
You're a shocker.
Have a go
at this bloody dingbat.
-Stan!
-Huh?
I think he's dead, mate.
Now he's dead.
-Yes!
-Oh, you prick!
-Oh, shit.
-Piss off, you mongrel dog.
Hey, Bennet!
-You want in on the next hand?
-Don't be stupid.
This, fellas...
is a gentlemen's game.
Be like trying to teach a bush
turkey how to drive a tractor.
His money's as good
as ours, Des.
Actually, it isn't.
My pay packet's only a third
of what you whitefellas get.
So, if you're happy to deal me
in on a two-thirds handicap...
It's never gonna happen, sambo.
So, you reckon you're worth
more than me, do you, Des?
Damn right, I do.
Knocked you on your ass today,
though, didn't I?
Fuck!
Leave it!
-Leave it, mate!
-Come on.
Get the fuck off me.
Leo. Leo!
-What the hell are you doing?
-Shh.
Don't...
Come on.
Hey.
Hazel.
Will.
Well? Are you just gonna
stand in the bushes all night?
So, what's your name?
Guess.
Mildred.
No.
-Agnes.
-No.
-Beryl.
-Nope.
-Blanche.
-God, no.
Bruce.
No!
-Charlotte.
-Yeah.
No.
You're a hard girl
to get to know.
Susie.
It's Susie.
You boys be
careful out there, okay?
All right,
lads, come on.
Let's go. Let's play.
Rightio.
Oi, pick 'em up
before you put 'em down.
Here we go. No, we don't.
Bad dreams?
The fuck are you
praying for, sunshine?
Not even halfway there yet.
Oh, you never know, mate.
-What the hell's that?
-It's a bloody air raid siren.
There go the 20 mils.
Don't worry, boys.
Knock them bastards
out of the sky in no time, eh?
Help!
Somebody help us!
Will!
Will, wake up. Will!
That's it! Yes! Yes!
That's it, Will!
Just breathe. Just breathe.
You're all right, mate.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey, hey.
Just breathe. You're all right.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
There goes our ride home.
Hey! No. Hey, listen!
Stay with me, Will.
Listen. Hey, stay with me.
I'm gonna jump back in
and start pushing
stuff towards you.
You need to tie it all down
using this rope.
Cut the lengths to size
using this.
Hey! Do you understand?
I need your help.
Okay.
You fucking dogs!
Hey! Hey!
Over here! Swim to me!
Leo?
Tommo?
What are youse two staring at?
-Is that his brains?
-What?
No, just bits of skin, I think.
Skull could be cracked, though.
Right, well,
I'm going for a walk.
No. You're not going anywhere.
You're gonna stay
right here, okay?
-Where's the boat?
-She's sunk, Tommo.
There's no boat, mate. Here.
Ow.
Ow! Ow, ow, ow.
Jesus Christ!
Leo?
What is that sound?
That sounds like a wolf.
It's not a bloody wolf, Tommo.
Shut up, will you?
It's getting closer.
It's getting closer!
Who goes there?
It's Thompson,
O'Conner, and Bennet!
What's that god-awful noise?
Bobby's bloody
broken air raid siren!
Can you fellas
just keep making noise
so we can find you?
How's that?
That'll do it.
Shut that bloody
yowling up, will ya?
Tommo. That's enough.
Who is that? Tommo?
What's up with him?
Head wound. It's pretty bad.
What happened to your float?
Fucking Japs.
Zeroes machine-gunned
the shit out of us.
Stan took one in the face.
Bobby's gutshot.
Oi. You fellas
got any medical supplies?
All we've got is bandages.
You got any morphine?
Sorry, boys. No morphine.
Got any smokes?
No.
It's a pretty sweet-looking
raft you got there, boys.
What do you say
we jump on board?
Keep everyone together.
Come on up.
We can't be
the only ones left.
Nearly 200 men
got on that bloody ship.
We gotta find them.
Hey!
What if there's still
wounded fellas out there, eh?
Anybody still out there would
have made it over to us by now.
Where's the boat?
Okay.
So we've got one Sten gun,
three grenades,
tin of peaches, a can of petrol,
a knife,
a pair of rescue flares,
and no water.
Right.
So this is the Timor Sea.
This... is Timor.
This here's Darwin.
I reckon we're here.
How do you figure that,
bookworm?
Well, a Corvette's
cruising speed's 12 knots,
which converts
to 13.8 miles per hour.
-We've been at sea--
-Yeah, okay, smart-ass.
How long before they pick us up?
-They gotta find us first.
-'Course they'll bloody find us.
We're in the middle
of a fog bank.
You couldn't find us
when we were ten yards away.
This shit'll clear up
in a couple hours.
Clear up, will it?
With what wind?
I'm not feeling any wind, Des.
Listen, sea fog like this
can last for days.
Especially out here.
Why don't we just take the boat?
The boat is sunk, Thompson.
I told you, it's not an option.
What the hell was that?
Fish, maybe?
Current's an issue.
Every hour,
we drift further away
from where they'll be looking.
Then again,
we are drifting home,
so if we can just survive
out here for a few extra days,
then, who knows?
So you're
sayin' all we have to do
is hang out on this thing
until we end up back in Darwin?
They'll send
rescue planes, but, eh?
Yeah, they'll send
the rescue planes, for sure.
-But that's--
-Needle in a haystack.
-Even without this fog.
-Right.
Those torpedoes
hit pretty hard and fast.
They might not have had time
to send out an SOS.
That's what I'm sayin'.
If we can just find the boat--
The boat is sunk, you dickhead!
So, what are youse two
bloody saying? Hmm?
That we should just give up?
-Is that what you're saying?
-All we're saying is
that it might take them a little
longer to find us, that's all.
How far is it
to Bathurst Island, you reckon?
Hundred and eighty...
190 miles, maybe?
We got Buckley's chance
of paddling that far.
What if we had a motorboat?
What if we had
a bloody luxury cruiser,
O'Conner, you turnip?
Don't have a motorboat,
do we?
There's one right over there.
That thing might get us home.
All right.
Who's up for a swim, then?
Well, it ain't gonna be me,
is it?
Oh, my God!
What the fuck was that?
Shark. Big one.
Oh, Jesus!
Did he just...
Did he just
get eaten by a shark?
Bobby!
Um...
Any ideas?
Anyone?
Oh! Hey! There he is!
Bobby! Bobby!
Swim! Swim!
Bobby, swim! Come on!
Well, this is fucked.
You see how bloody big
that thing was?
It's a goddamn monster,
that is.
Never seen a shark
like that before.
It's a great white.
Female.
How can you tell?
Size.
Twenty-footer, I reckon.
The males don't get that big.
Oh, you're joking.
So we're standing
on a pile of shrapnel,
and you're telling me there's
a pissed-off 20-foot fish
-down there?
-Shh.
Keep your voice down.
Sound travels fast
through the water.
You saying there's a fish
down there listening to us?
She's not just listening, Des.
She's hunting. She's waiting.
She's waiting
for a reason to attack.
Sharks
are attracted to two things,
blood and movement.
If we stay quiet and still
and don't bleed too much,
she might leave us alone.
How do you know
so much about 'em?
Archie!
Stan!
Stan, swim to me!
Help me! Please!
-Grab my hand!
-I got you!
-Pull me up! Don't let go!
Shoot it! Fucking shoot it!
Grenade! Grenade!
Throw the grenade!
The femoral artery's cut.
We need to put pressure on it.
Then do it!
Jesus Christ, just do it!
Hold him down!
Hold him the fuck down!
-Will, what's next?
-I'm not a bloody medic!
Okay, just make a decision
and do something.
We have to tie it off.
Give me your belt.
Come on!
Tommo!
Tommo, get the fuck away!
Come on, you toothy bastard.
Show us your fin.
-Bandages, Teddy!
-Okay.
You're all right, mate.
Just focus on your breathing.
Hold him! Hold him!
Here you go!
I'll hold that, I'll hold that.
You lost your leg!
Stopped the flow.
He stopped the flow.
It's locked off.
It's locked off. It's all right.
It okay, mate.
Your rugby career's
probably fucked, but...
you're gonna live.
-Right, Teddy?
-I lost my leg!
I lost my leg!
We need to wrap him up
in that canvas
and wash the blood
off the raft.
Otherwise,
it's gonna come straight back.
I lost my leg!
I lost my fucking leg!
Maybe that grenade
scared it off for good, eh?
Nah.
She'll be back.
The sea's glowing.
Get away from the edge,
you dopey bastard.
Looks like
the moon's down there!
Gonna get your head
bitten off, you mug!
Bioluminescence.
Chemical reaction
makes the water glow.
It's beautiful, eh?
If he doesn't get help,
he's gonna bleed out.
He may not last the night.
Without that boat,
Stan's a dead man.
What are you up to?
I reckon I can get
all the way to that motor
without even
getting my feet wet.
You're mad, you bastard.
You'll get the chomp
before you make it halfway.
Not if I'm quick.
-He's gonna fucking die.
-Shut up, Des.
Come on.
Shoot it! Shoot it! Shoot it!
Holy fuck! Fuck!
Shoot it, Des!
Fucking shoot it!
Leo!
Leo! What are you doing?
Jump!
Pull!
One, two, three.
You lucky, lucky bastard.
Okay.
Fuel line's fucked.
It's not gonna turn over.
She's back.
What is that?
Bobby's siren.
It's lodged in her fin.
The fin? Eh?
You mean it's the bloody shark
out there making that sound?
What's it doin'?
She's circling.
It's a hunting technique.
Hunting who?
Winston fucking Churchill.
Who do you reckon, mate?
Quiet.
Don't make a sound.
It's right bloody under us!
It's right bloody under us.
She's testing us.
Seeing if she can
break it apart.
The fuck is she
picking on us for, eh?
There's dozens of fucking
dead bodies out there
for it to munch on.
Maybe she likes
fresh meat.
Put the lights out.
Turn 'em off! Turn 'em off!
That's it!
Give me the grenade!
Give me the fucking grenade!
-I'm gonna blow this fucker up!
-Wait! Just wait!
What do you mean, wait?
It's gonna rip this thing apart,
and then we are fucked.
There are two grenades left,
we need to make them count.
Stan!
What the fuck was that?
Agh, Jesus!
You blew up Stan,
you fucking idiot!
What? How did I do that?
The pin.
You pulled the pin,
and you let the grenade go!
Eh? No. No, no, no--
You fucking did!
I fucking saw you, you fucking--
Jesus! Look at this shit!
We have to
get this cleaned up.
Yeah.
We just kick him off, then.
Don't you kick him off,
you dog!
Don't you call me a dog.
-You're the dog, you rock ape!
-Hey!
-Don't you dare call him that!
-Piss off, idiot.
That man
rolled on a grenade for you.
He saved your fucking life!
What do you want me to do?
Sing him a song?
Fuck! Jesus! Fuck!
Just stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
You've got guts on you.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fellas...
I'm sure there's a way
we can get rid of Stan's body
in a respectful fashion.
Hell of a way to wake up.
I got a feeling it's gonna
be another long, bloody day.
We should divvy up
some of them peaches.
If we don't get something
in our guts soon,
this heat's gonna kill us.
What the hell is this?
Which one of you dirty bastards
ate all the goddamn peaches?
Tommy?
Did you eat all the peaches?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
There's heaps of peaches.
There's cans everywhere.
Yeah?
Where's that, Tommy?
-On the boat!
-Oh, you've killed us, mate.
You've bloody killed us.
Never thought
I'd go out like this.
Thought I'd catch a bullet,
for sure.
And there's the Sarge,
and he's banging on about
your medals and your mates
and your honor and...
here we are.
My old man was at Gallipoli.
There was no medal for him.
Did bring home
a big bit of shrapnel
stuck in his brain, though.
And that crazy bastard, right?
He used to run around
the house at night
screaming,
thinking we were all Turks.
He tried to kill me mum
and me sisters once.
So I learned how to fight.
What happened?
He hung himself, didn't he?
Best bloody day of my life.
And I sure as shit
ain't going out like that.
Here I am.
Big Des Kelly, dying of thirst.
Do you fellas know
you can drink your own urine?
Fair dinkum?
Yeah, that's what they reckon.
They say it'll give you
a couple extra days, anyway.
No bloody way
am I drinking my own piss.
Coupla extra days, they reckon?
Yeah.
That's what they reckon.
You're kidding me.
Bennet! You're not actually
gonna drink your own dick spit,
are you?
Mind your business, Des.
Oh, strewth! He's doing it.
He's bloody doing it!
You grotty bastard.
This grotty bastard's
gonna live a couple of days
longer than you, mate.
Ah!
Got some color to it, eh?
Like a...
Mmm, like a nice Irish whiskey.
Pungent.
Oh, bit of corkage, yeah?
Bit yeasty?
Get it in ya, mate.
Cheers, boys.
You minging dog.
That's better.
That is the filthiest thing
that I have ever seen
a living man do, Bennet.
No way in hell I'm doing that.
So refreshing.
God help us all.
You've gotta be bloody kidding!
Fill it up, you dog!
Fill it up!
Fucking... grab these!
What's that gonna do?
Archie?
Tommo!
Yeah.
Leo?
What are you doin'?
Archie!
Let me go!
Archie's down there!
-Who the hell is Archie?
-That shark wants me!
What are you
talking about, Leo?
What's he on about?
-I have to go down!
-Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey...
Just stop for a second, okay?
I'm not strong like you.
None of us are.
Without you, we're gonna die.
I don't want to die, Leo.
I want to go home.
I just want to go home.
Is that a bloody plane?
There!
Hey!
Here!
-Here! Here!
-Here!
The engine...
It's too high-pitched.
It's the wrong sound.
That's not one of ours.
Help me.
For Christ sake, help me!
-Help me! Help me!
-I don't know what I can do.
It's coming back.
Oh, fuck it.
Des! What are you doing?
Gutshot...
I need you to check
it's gone through.
There's an exit hole.
I'll get it wrapped.
I'll be goddamned!
I think you hit
the bloody thing!
I hope you fucking drown,
you mongrel dog.
What happened to Teddy?
Shark got him.
I wasn't asking you, was I?
He got the chomp, mate.
End of.
Bloke
was covered in blood.
Why'd you take him in?
You pushed him towards it.
To save yourself.
I saw you do it.
He was a goner.
Had no chance.
Your own mate?
He would've bled out
in ten minutes.
Your own mate. You used him
as a fucking human shield.
What the fuck
am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to protect him!
And you just let him die.
Hey, Leo, just calm down, eh?
Hey.
Will?
Buy you a drink?
Sure.
You get this round.
Next one's on me.
Deal.
That's a drink you owe me.
I'm good for it.
I killed him.
I just killed him.
The sea took him.
Can't get it out of me head.
I'm sorry for what I done.
I don't wanna die.
You're not gonna die, Des.
We're going home, all right?
We're going home.
What is that?
Is that...
Oh, you gotta be
fucking joking.
Will...
You got that last grenade?
What are you waiting for?
Kill him.
What?
What do you think he's
gonna do when he gets here?
Shake your hand?
Eh!
This is war.
He's surrendering.
They don't surrender.
Will...
You need to make a decision.
No.
It's not right.
Yeah. Righto.
-Give it to me.
-Just wait!
The boat...
I reckon it might be time
for that last drink, eh?
Where'd you get that?
I told you.
Next round's on me.
Gimme that.
Hoo!
That's got some kick to it.
Oh, God! That's rank!
Give me a cold schooner
of Foster's any day.
Foster's?
You dirty bastard.
VB, mate. All the way.
Foster's.
I'd rather drink my own piss.
You'd be used to that,
wouldn't you, mate?
Fog's cleared up.
You can see the sky again.
It's beautiful.
Yeah. I guess.
I'm ready.
Is that a toolbox?
Leo, I think
it's a bloody toolbox, mate.
Jesus! Leo! Your arm!
I did it, Will.
I blew that fucker up.
You crazy bugger.
What the hell
were you thinking?
-Hey, Will?
-Yeah? Yeah, mate?
You got any of that booze left?
Shit.
Sorry, mate,
I guess I dropped it.
Well, that's another drink
you owe me.
Next one's on me, mate.
Next one's on me.
Let's go home.